Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
Do you have to apologize
because you said something mean?
The sooner, the better.
Apologies expire too.
They'll mean nothing
if you wait too long.
Where did she go?
Where is she?
Is she on the rooftop?
No, it's not messy. I was gentle.
I'll think of a wish, Da-reum.
"Da-reum"?
What brings you here this late?
I came because I missed you.
Ms. Nam, why are you up here?
What?
Oh, I...
I came to get this banner
then ran into Director Lee
by coincidence.
Please excuse me.
Goodbye, then.
Bye, Da-reum.
Aren't you being a bit too friendly?
After all, she's an employee.
I wasn't, really.
You patted her head
and spoke in a casual tone.
Do you think she's your fan?
She had something in her hair,
so I just pulled it out.
We're at work.
I'm worried people will talk.
Are you jealous?
Jealous, my foot.
All right. I'll be more careful.
- Sorry.
- Watch out.
Okay.
EPISODE 4
Oh, my. Ms. Da-reum.
Why are you taking that?
Wait, Ms. Da-reum.
You must be on Team Chan.
- Right?
- Sorry?
No, not really.
My friend needed this
for banner recycling.
I am
on Team Ha-gi.
- Really?
- Yes.
Why is the management
more popular than the celebrity
in this company?
Right?
- Goodbye, then.
- Goodbye.
Have a great night.
So heavy.
Don't be so weak, Nam Da-reum.
You're carrying your Chan.
I got this. It's not heavy at all.
Ms. Nam.
What are you doing?
My friend asked me to bring this.
So are you carrying that home?
Yes, sir.
I'm strong. I'll be fine.
All right, then.
Did he actually leave
because I said I was fine?
Hop in.
I'll give you a ride.
Thank you.
It feels like
there are three of us in the car.
Maybe I shouldn't have hopped in.
It's so awkward.
There's something I must say to you.
Sure. Please fire away.
Actually
I have misunderstood you for a while.
What kind of misunderstanding?
SE Corporation plans to launch
a fashion platform like ours soon
and they've been taking our brands.
- Are you serious?
- Appello's data had been leaked
so I got a bit sensitive.
I thought you were hiding
the fact that you worked there
to infiltrate my business.
Wait a second.
Did you think
I was some kind of spy or something?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for saying
all those harsh words to you.
- I sincerely...
- Sorry.
He got me.
How did you figure out...
I was a spy?
What?
I'm just joking.
I can't believe you had
such a misunderstanding.
It's not like I'm Black Widow.
That's why I'm apologizing.
Please stop laughing.
Well, I want to stop too.
But it's too funny.
Don't worry about it, Mr. Kang.
I love Appello way
more than I liked them.
I believe
our company will grow much bigger
and far surpass SE Corporation.
- Do you mean it?
- Of course, I do.
Wait, should I help you find the spy?
- You?
- Yes.
Who knows?
I might catch a trace of that punk.
Sure, I guess.
Let me know if you see
anything suspicious.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best.
Who is it?
Who could be doing such a thing?
Gosh, I've only seen
people do this on TV.
I'm so excited.
PROJECT OUTSTANDING EMPLOYEE
"Help out
with the logistical task for Go.co."
"Find the spy..."
FIND THE SPY
"Appointed as
Mr. Kang's secret
agent."
I mean
I stood in that pouring rain
and worked so hard
on editing the video.
What? A spy?
Jeez.
The more I get to know Mr. Kang,
the more I realize
he's tough to read.
2025 ONLINE FASHION SHOW FINAL REPORT
I'm just joking.
I can't believe you had
such a misunderstanding.
It's not like I'm Black Widow.
What was so funny about my apology?
She always laughs when she sees me.
It may be because
she feels comfortable around you.
Jeez, you startled me.
Alert me before you respond, Luni.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Anyway.
- What did you say?
- It may be because
she feels comfortable around you.
Or she may have feelings for you.
"Feelings for me"?
I am
on Team Ha-gi.
I am on Team Ha-gi.
And?
Do you find yourself thinking
about the moments you spent together?
- Yes.
- That means your brain
releases a lot of dopamine
when you think of that person.
You're in the process of forming
the early stages of attachment.
Congratulations!
What?
No, it's not me. It was her.
She was the one who laughed at me.
That's even stronger proof.
A woman's smile is a social cue
and a positive biological reaction.
It must mean
your genes are quite attractive.
Forget it. That's enough.
OUCH!
You're really nosy for an AI bot.
I SCRAPED MY KNEES TODAY
WHILE POWERWALKING IN SADNESS
THEN A GIRL CAME AND ASKED,
"ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?"
EVERYTHING WILL GO WELL
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING
I'M ROOTING FOR YOU
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY
COCOTALK
YOU HAVE A NEW MESSAGE
What?
What do I do?
Girls!
Girls, I need help.
What do I do?
- Why?
- What is it?
"It's the weekend.
What are you up to?"
CHAN
- "Wish"?
- I know, right?
You two also have no idea
what this means, do you?
Why would he suddenly ask this?
- It's clear, right?
- So obvious.
What is?
Namda, make up your mind.
Will you go as a woman or as a fan?
Show up where as a woman or a fan?
Oh, come on!
You're so slow.
What do you think this means?
It's obviously a date.
A date?
Like an actual date?
What do you mean
he's asking me out on a date?
Jeez. You're so slow. Come on.
Of course, I'll show up as a fan.
How am I a woman to him?
Namda, listen up.
A fan is a woman too.
Is there a particular wine
you're looking for?
It's not for me. It's a gift.
But there are
way too many different kinds of wine.
Do you know
what the other person prefers?
No, let's see.
He's a man in his 30s.
And he's rather thoughtful.
A man in his 30s
who's the thoughtful type.
Just give me something really good.
By the way, is this a gift
for someone you like?
Yes.
Sir, would you like a recommendation?
- Shush.
- Sorry?
- You should tell him.
- Be quiet.
Wait, if it's for someone you like,
what wine should you get?
I have a recommendation.
This will be perfect.
This wine is said to help
one's love come true.
Help love come true?
- Gosh, it's not like that.
- It must be like that.
- No way.
- This is it.
- Gosh, it's not.
- But it is!
You're holding this so tightly.
Well, you gave it to me.
It helps one's love come true.
My gosh!
CAFE RIMONDE
It should be around here.
FILMING IN PROGRESS
BITTER SWEET
Bitter Sweet?
Wait, is he filming here?
I went through so much
just to see Lee Chan.
Whatever. I'm done.
"Lee Chan"?
Is he here?
Why are you out here?
- What?
- Come. We're about to roll.
Why would I go?
Aren't you an extra?
No, I'm not.
- No, this is the outfit.
- It's not me.
Man, this is driving me crazy.
We need to match continuity.
Then can you help me out just once?
- Sorry?
- Just once.
Me?
- I'll take that.
- Okay.
Now, stand here.
Please help us out.
Keep walking away from the camera
and Chan will come and say
"I'm sorry. You are not the person
I was looking for."
We're already running out of time.
Let's get it in one take.
Let's roll.
Stand by.
And cue.
Cue.
Cut!
Back to your place.
Hey, can you walk more naturally?
- What?
- Why is your walk so stiff?
Okay?
Fine.
You must be nervous, Da-reum.
Just relax and think
that you're walking toward me. Okay?
You got this.
- Okay.
- Take two.
- Let's roll again.
Now, slate it.
- And...
- Wait.
Cue.
I'm sorry. You are...
the one I was looking for.
Cut!
What's wrong, Chan?
You got the line wrong.
Goodness. I'm sorry.
Let me do that again. I'm sorry.
Let's do another take.
- Oh, wow.
- Right here.
Seo-jun, are you putting
stickers on his face?
Great job.
Keep doing that for me. Thanks.
Put some more on him.
This is great. I'm so happy.
I'm even happier to see Ha-gi
for the first time in ages.
I'm sorry to bother you
on your day off.
But my kids were begging to see you
and asked me to drag you here.
Seo-jun and Seo-yeon,
stop bothering him now.
You'll make
my life at work difficult.
- Go over there and play.
- Yes, go there and run around.
Yes, you can run all you want.
It's okay, Seong-wook.
It's nice to get out for a change.
And it's nice to see
Mrs. Chae after so long.
Gosh, that brings me back
to the old days.
When you just started working
you'd chase me around like a chick,
calling me, "Ms. Chae."
And you went around
calling me, "Mr. CEO."
If only my business hadn't failed.
Respect him at work
and watch what you say.
We have a mountain of debt
because of that ruined business.
Please show my husband your favor,
CEO Kang Ha-gi.
- A raise, please.
- Don't mention it.
I'm so grateful for his help.
I should've planned
this get-together sooner.
Come over to my place.
I'll treat you to dinner.
Really?
I'd love to eat at your place.
Stop. What do you mean?
Why? What did I say just now?
- You'd love to eat there?
- No.
I think the kids are fighting.
Is this it?
I can't see anything.
- You found it all right.
- Yes.
- Get in.
- Okay.
- Shall we?
Just drop me at any subway station
on your way.
What do you mean?
- You have to grant me a wish.
- What?
But back there...
Did you think
my wish was
for you to show up at my shoot?
I wanted to get some good food
with you after the shoot.
But the shoot ran long
and I had to cancel my reservation.
Come to my place. I'll cook for you.
Pardon?
Your place?
Yes.
You mean
I'm going to your place?
Yes, it's right around the corner.
What's going on? Am I dreaming?
My heart is about to burst.
- Buckle up.
- What? Okay.
Tech neck, rounded shoulders,
and a herniated disc too.
You're a whole mess.
You should pick up
a workout like Pilates.
Why would a guy do Pilates?
Without this curve,
my neck would be stiff.
My shoulders are obviously straight,
and so is my back.
I'm totally fine.
SMOOTH
APPARATUS PILATES
POSTURE CORRECTION
Smooth?
HYBRID PILATES
The doctor was right.
My neck hurts. It does.
This is amazing.
- This way.
- Okay.
Walking into his place together
makes us feel like a couple...
Get a grip on yourself, Da-reum.
He only invited me home
because he can't eat outside freely.
Cut it out with your filthy delusion.
What should I make?
CREAM RISOTTO
2022 GOLDEN CREST AWARD
BEST ACTOR LEE CHAN
Yes, I remember.
That was the Rookie Award he won
after he had just started acting.
I cried a river back then.
- Da-reum.
- Yes?
You can go upstairs and take a tour.
May I do that?
Of course.
I'll call you when I'm done.
Okay.
- Feel free to relax.
- Okay.
What the heck.
CREAM GNOCCHI
Please excuse me.
My gosh.
This was the shoot
he did with Photographer Yeong-su.
This wasn't in the pictorial.
Am I really allowed to see
these unreleased photos?
Look at his eyes. Insane.
So this is where
he streams live from time to time.
It's so cool.
He's so great.
Does he still make music?
Da-reum, dinner's ready.
Come on down.
Okay.
CREAM GNOCCHI, FISH ROE PASTA
Did you make all these?
You're amazing.
- You're teasing me.
- I'm not.
It's fine as long as it's good.
I tried doing my best,
but I don't know how good it is.
Thank you.
It's really good.
It's like a dish
made by a famous chef.
Really? I did get some help.
Eat up, Da-reum. Here.
Thank you.
I'm too nervous
to enjoy this right now.
I hope you weren't lying
when you said it was good.
I'm just a bit nervous.
- If it's too much, just leave it.
- No, it's not.
Usually, I would've finished
all of these in three minutes.
One second.
YOON CHO-YI
How's work?
It's probably not easy
to work with Ha-gi.
It's not.
When he comes next to me
I get chills down my spine.
He's someone
I can't seem to get close to.
He's like that.
He never lets his guard down
around people.
Yes, exactly.
His office is impeccably neat
right down to every single pen.
He's probably like that at home too.
Right?
Hey, this is really good.
Eat up.
- Go.
- Let's go.
- Guys, no running.
- Don't you love his place?
This isn't our place!
- I wish it were.
- Hey.
The one thing Ha-gi can't stand
is anything
that's hectic and disorderly.
He rarely ever invites people over.
Sorry, Ha-gi.
- It's okay.
- Stop running!
What's this?
- But one funny thing about him.
- Hey! No!
- Uncle Ha-gi...
Fine.
Go ahead.
He has the weakest spot
for people within his boundary.
He was really nosy when we were kids.
You mean, Mr. Kang?
That's hard to imagine.
The reason we got close
was thanks to his nosiness.
I wasn't looking to make friends
but Ha-gi
kept pestering me.
I transferred
when I was in 10th grade
and had trouble adapting.
I got bullied too.
- There you are, my friend.
- What?
What are you doing?
Time to pay
this week's friendship fee.
Cut it out.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, sorry.
He's a player on my team.
Do you have business with him?
Darn it.
Ha-gi was the school president,
who got good grades
and was good at basketball.
The typical golden boy.
Let's go.
I'll get you later.
Hey.
We really need
more players on our team.
Can you play one game with us?
What?
- Come on.
- Let's split into teams.
- Okay.
- Come on.
The losers treat the winners
to snacks at the snack bar.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Hey, Chan.
Time for a snack bar run.
Hey.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
What?
- Come on.
- And he was a warm-hearted kid
who couldn't see anyone get left out.
- Go, Ha-gi.
Over here!
- Nice job!
- Oh, no.
You got this, Ha-gi.
Just do your thing. Yes.
Yes, that's it.
- Nice job!
- Okay!
Great job!
Nice job!
That was awesome, Ha-gi!
- Awesome job.
- Let's go.
Thanks to him,
I gradually changed too.
- Hey, wait.
- Let's go!
What do you want to eat?
What do you feel like?
It was a lot of fun
- to spend time with Ha-gi.
- I don't know. What should we eat?
I even stuck around at his place
and had dinner every day.
It smells great.
- My parents always came home late.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Hey, you made bulgogi.
Yes, because it's your favorite.
Eat up.
Just as you helped me
overcome my darkest times
you had Mr. Kang with you.
He is
my one and only friend.
Maybe everyone wanted
to be friends with you
but you just didn't realize it?
No way. I wasn't that popular.
- You're lying.
- I'm serious.
Ha-gi was much more popular.
Really?
I guess it shows
whether a person
has always been loved
or they haven't.
Everyone leaves me in the end.
I wouldn't.
For the last ten years... No.
To be exact
I've liked only you
for the last 11 years and ten months.
I have never set my eyes
on anyone else, not even once.
And I will continue to like only you.
Wait, what have I done just now?
Look how overwhelmed he is.
I mean
as a fan.
Completely as a fan.
Just as a fan.
Thanks for liking me.
I'm not even a big deal
but thank you for your support
over such a long time.
Thank you.
I want to thank you too.
And I never thought
I'd see a day like this in my life.
Da-reum.
Can I ask you for a favor?
What do you think about this song?
I love it.
It reminds me of old D.N.X songs.
D.N.X.
I only meant how the song sounded.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have brought it up.
No, don't say that.
I'm so grateful
that you still think about D.N.X.
Da-reum.
Do you also want us to reunite?
Yes, of course.
All D-Angels would feel the same.
It's actually meant
to be a D.N.X fan song.
If we ever reunite
I want to sing it with everyone.
Chan...
I also did the mixing.
Would you like to listen to it?
Oh, yes. I'd love to listen to it.
What's this?
What is this vibe?
You're so slow.
What do you think this means?
It's obviously a date.
A fan is a woman too.
What do I do?
- Da-reum.
- Yes?
What are you guys doing?
What are you doing here?
Am I in the wrong place?
Is it you this time?
How was the fan meet with him?
Did you enjoy it
to your heart's content?
- Pardon?
- Come out. Let's talk outside.
Did I
walk in
when you were expecting something?
Hey, Yoon Cho-yi.
Oh, no. I guess I was right.
Did you really think
there was something going on?
- She's cute.
- What are you saying? Get out.
No, I'll leave.
Thank you for everything today,
Director Lee.
I'm sorry, but if you don't mind,
I'll get going first.
Da-reum.
Chan, I'm sorry.
I was such a bother today.
You should get inside.
- Da-reum, that's not it...
- Chan.
Can you
just let me go?
I feel
mortified right now.
Why did I dress up?
This is humiliating.
How did you get in?
The passcode to your door is
still the same.
You must've kept it
because you wanted me to come in.
The person who was just here...
I had her over for a meal
because she was a special fan.
She's not someone
you can talk to like that.
Have you ever had me over
for anything when we were dating?
What does she mean to you?
Why are you treating her
like she's special?
She rooted for me for ten years,
but I've never done anything for her.
Right.
You have always been like that.
You act like a good person
on the outside.
You think you won't hurt other people
like you hurt me?
Whoever you choose to date
you'll still be the same.
Ha-gi, thanks for everything today.
See you next time.
- Bye.
- Say bye to Uncle Ha-gi.
- Bye, Uncle Ha-gi.
See you.
- Bye.
- Take care.
See you. Bye.
A sticker remover.
Where can I get it?
BEAUTY TRIO GROUP CHAT
Namda! Are you still with Chan?
Are you alive or not?
Why aren't you answering?
BITTER SWEET
I hope they aren't fighting
because of me.
I doubt it.
I mean nothing to them.
BITTER SWEET
Oh, no. I guess I was right.
Did you really think
there was something going on?
This is humiliating.
Come to your senses, Nam Da-reum.
You're just one of his numerous fans.
INCOMING CALL
CHAN
Where on earth can I get it?
Wait...
Ms. Nam!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Why aren't you watching
where you're going?
Why did you cross the road
without checking the traffic light?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't see it.
I really
didn't see it.
I know I was wrong.
If you yell at me like that
I don't know what to say.
Sorry for getting mad at you.
I was startled too.
No, I'm sorry.
Did
something bad happen?
No.
Today was
the happiest day of my life.
Something
I'd always dreamed of
happened to me.
But
I didn't realize dreams end...
once I wake up.
Let's go.
I'll take you home.
Okay.
Your bag.
Oh, that's right.
What's wrong with me?
INKUK HOSPITAL
You sprained your ligament.
You need to wear it
for at least two weeks.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
These are what I could find for now.
I thought you might need them.
What are they?
RUBBER GLOVES
What's this for?
Shower with that on for tonight.
And tomorrow...
Take this off now.
Okay.
I'll take it off.
Oh, Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang, let me help you.
Are you okay?
Whenever I'm with you,
I have to watch my back and front.
I just can't let my guard down.
I'd better get going.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kang.
What am I going to do now?
I got into trouble again.
Well...
He just wanted to thank me
for being his fan for so long.
We had dinner at his house.
That's all.
Wait, you went to his house?
How can you say
that's not a big deal?
Normally, you would've made a scene
saying you couldn't believe it.
But why are you so calm?
- You're suspicious.
No, I'm not.
I couldn't be happier.
I'm on cloud nine.
When you experience
something completely unbelievable
you become surprisingly calm.
If that's the case,
I'm happy for you.
I was worried for nothing.
Did you see Namda's terrible acting?
Something happened for sure.
Something happened to her.
She was excited to meet Chan.
What the heck happened?
I wonder if Mr. Kang is okay.
He'd think I'm a total nuisance.
He wouldn't use those red gloves.
What was I thinking?
I'm such an idiot.
So what happened to your arm?
It was fine until the weekend.
A dog came at me.
How big was the dog
to leave your arm like that?
Well, it was
about the size of a Pomeranian.
A Pomeranian?
You mean a Pomeranian?
Mr. Kang.
We have a seat for you here.
Come on. Join us.
Have a seat.
Excuse me. We'll get beef brisket
doenjang soup and jeyuk.
Okay.
Mr. Kang, your arm...
Mr. Kang, what happened to your arm?
Let me tell you what happened.
A Pomeranian attacked his arm.
- A Pomeranian?
- Yes, a Pomeranian.
- The small dog?
- Yes, the small dog.
- The cute one?
- Very cute.
A lovely Pomeranian?
The lovely Pomeranian.
I fell.
It must be uncomfortable, Mr. Kang.
Still, you're lucky
it's your left arm
not your right arm.
I'm left-handed.
Oh, I see.
Let's eat.
- Enjoy.
- Enjoy your meal.
Oh, no. What do we do?
- Here.
- Thank you.
I'm worried.
Mr. Kang.
Do you want me to feed you?
No, thank you.
You're eating nothing but rice.
I like rice.
No, let me feed you. Here.
Mr. Kang, the overseas VC wants
to hear back from us by today.
If you confirm it
I'll send the file now.
What do you think?
I want to fix a few pages.
Give me a few minutes.
Bye.
Shoot.
APPELLO CEO KANG HA-GI
Mr. Kang, I'm sorry about all the...
No.
What should I say?
Mr. Kang, if you need anything,
call me anytime...
No.
Why do I keep causing Mr. Kang harm
and nothing ever works out
when I'm with him?
What should I say in the apology?
Think. Think with your brain.
CALLING APPELLO CEO KANG HA-GI
INCOMING CALL
MS. NAM DA-REUM
Hello?
Ms. Nam?
Ms. Nam Da-reum?
Yes, Mr. Kang.
You must be off work by now.
Yes. What are you calling me for
at this hour?
Well, that's...
Your arm must be causing you
a lot of discomfort.
I meant to text you
because I was concerned.
But somehow I ended up calling you.
Yes, it's very uncomfortable.
Because of my arm
I couldn't even fix
the urgent proposal.
Really?
That's not good.
I'll go to your house now.
- We live in the same neighborhood.
- What?
But...
You could just help me
at a cafe nearby...
No, you have an injured arm.
How would you bring your laptop
and materials with you?
Just wait. I'll leave soon.
Ms. Nam Da-reum. Nam...
Ms. Nam... Ms. Nam?
Shoot.
This is my chance to make up
for being a nuisance.
Mr. Kang, just wait.
My 600-character-per-minute fingers
are coming.
This is Ha-gi's favorite wine.
I'm here.
Mr. Kang, I'm here.
Okay.
- Hello.
- Ms. Nam.
- That was fast.
- Yes.
Your house is so close.
It's only 500m away from my house.
- Did you run here?
- Yes.
You need to send the proposal soon.
Oh, thank you.
- Where do you want me to work on it?
- What?
Here. No, there.
Oh, how about next to your laptop?
- Mr. Kang, are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
- Mr. Kang.
- Yes?
Is this the one?
Oh, yes.
Then...
It's inconvenient
to look at the monitors this way.
I'll move next to you.
What do you need to add?
- Mr. Kang?
- Yes?
Did you hear what I said?
You need to tell me what to add.
Oh, yes. Right.
- How did I miss that?
- Focus.
Okay.
Focus.
I wanted to add some data
to the original pitch deck.
The CEO of this VC considers
CSR important.
Are you trying to emphasize
Appello's mission of mutual growth?
Yes, that's correct.
Then, how about using the last
online fashion show as an example?
It has a visual impact
and emphasizes
that we're a fashion company.
That's a good idea.
Yes, I'll go with that then.
Delete this.
- Say that it was done in real time.
- Okay.
Add real time...
Again...
THIS IS THE FINAL VERSION
SEND
SUCCESSFULLY SENT
It's sent.
What?
What a relief.
I've sent the edited version.
Can you check it?
I was able to handle
the urgent matter thanks to you.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
You're in that state because of me.
This is the least I could do.
By the way, Mr. Kang.
What are these?
Well, my friend's kids came over
the other day.
Do you want me to remove them?
- You will?
- Yes.
No, it's not necessary...
Until your arm gets all better
can you stand watching them?
Well...
Honestly
it's torture.
Exactly. Let me remove them for you.
With this.
Well...
- Can you take this off too?
- Sure!
Keep it up.
Good.
DA-REUM
Let me take you home. It's late.
Oh, no. Don't bother.
It's only 500m away.
You have an injured arm. Stay home.
- But still...
- Oh, right!
My mom said I shouldn't visit
anyone's house empty-handed.
I almost forgot.
- Thank you, but...
- No.
It's from my heart.
You didn't have to...
It's not for me. It's a gift.
By any chance, is this a gift
for someone you like?
Yes.
This will be perfect.
This wine is said to help
one's love come true.
Is it a gift for someone you like?
This wine is said to help
one's love come true.
Let me put this away.
Sure.
This wine is said to help
one's love come true.
Does she...
No, it must be a coincidence.
I am on Team Ha-gi.
Team Ha-gi...
I am...
I am on Team Ha-gi.
Well...
- Wait here just a second.
- But...
Luni.
Yes, did you call me?
Please keep your voice down.
What does it mean
if someone gives you a bottle of wine
and says it's from her heart?
In fact, that wine is said
to help one's love come true.
That means more than interest.
It's normally used
to express a head-on romance.
A head-on romance?
It's often used to express love
for the other person indirectly.
That woman definitely likes you.
You guys should date.
So she
likes me?
That woman definitely likes you.
So she...
...likes me?
Definitely likes you.
I like you.
I LIKE
I LIKE YOU
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPILOGUE
Who is she?
Ms. Da-reum.
- Can you check over here too?
- Yes, I'm coming.
She randomly puts her hands on me.
She smiles at me
every time she sees me.
- Get a grip, Kang Ha-gi.
- What...
Mr. Kang!
Why are you taking me with you?
Work is only an excuse.
You're totally into each other.
I just wanted to see you,
even if it was like this.
Mr. Kang's on a business trip.
Ms. Da-reum, spit it out here.
With Ms. Da-reum?
Be honest with me today.
Do you see me as a man?
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs